http://www.marksandharrison.com/privacy-policy/

(800) 283-2202
HomeAbout Us Firm OverviewOur FoundersHow We Are PaidFirm NewsCommunity InvolvementAttorney ReferralsCareersOur Professionals Our AttorneysFirm ManagementStaff DirectoryPractice Areas Personal InjuryTractor Trailer AccidentsCar AccidentsSocial Security DisabilityVeterans’ Disability BenefitsWorkers’ CompensationNursing Home NeglectMotorcycle AccidentsWrongful DeathPremises LiabilitySee All Practice AreasTestimonialsResults Our ResultsUnusual CasesResources BlogVideosFAQsTeen Safe Driving EbookMotorcycle GuideHow To Vote in VirginiaContact Us
MENU
HomeAbout Us Firm OverviewOur FoundersHow We Are PaidFirm NewsCommunity InvolvementAttorney ReferralsCareersOur Professionals Our AttorneysFirm ManagementStaff DirectoryPractice Areas Personal InjuryTractor Trailer AccidentsCar AccidentsSocial Security DisabilityVeterans’ Disability BenefitsWorkers’ CompensationNursing Home NeglectMotorcycle AccidentsWrongful DeathPremises LiabilitySee All Practice AreasTestimonialsResults Our ResultsUnusual CasesResources BlogVideosFAQsTeen Safe Driving EbookMotorcycle GuideHow To Vote in VirginiaContact Us
Home Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Online Privacy PolicyThank you for visiting MarksandHarrison.com, which is a website owned and operated by the law firm of Marks & Harrison. As part of our commitment to privacy, we have adopted the following online privacy policy for this site.This policy applies to any online forms submitted by you through our website. It explains how your personally identifiable information is collected at this site, and how we use that information. By submitting an online form through MarksandHarrison.com, you are accepting the practices described in this online privacy policy.Online Contact FormsBy submitting personally identifiable information through our online forms at MarksandHarrison.com, you are providing Marks & Harrison with your name, e-mail address, phone number and personal case information. This information is, in turn, used by Marks & Harrison solely for the purposes of determining whether you have a legal claim and whether the law firm or its affiliates are in a position to be of assistance to you. We will not use this information for any purpose other than what has been stated or intended.Security of Your InformationMarks & Harrison recognizes the importance of providing security for all personally identifiable information collected through this website. To protect against the loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration of this information, our firm permits only authorized internal staff (attorneys, co-counsel, case managers, paralegals, witnesses and other agents of the law firm) to have access to this information. Marks & Harrison retains this contact information electronically. The information is stored in a secured network in the same fashion as all other client personal and medical data.Our Policy for Protecting Your Online PrivacyThis website, marksandharrison.com, uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third-party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site.This could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who have not completed a task on our site such as using the contact form to submit an inquiry. Advertising could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page or a site in the Google Display Network.Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the marksandharrison.com website. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you by using the Google Ad Preferences page. You can also opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by adjusting cookie settings or permanently using a browser plug-in.marksandharrison.com uses Google Analytics to help analyze how visitors use the site. The tool uses “cookies.” These are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form, including Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp and number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track the user’s movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for marksandharrison.com.As part of our commitment to transparency and your privacy, we provide the following links to opt-out of cookies provided by both our first-party ad server and many third-party advertising partners who may be engaging in online behavioral advertising:First-Party Opt-out – Please visit this link to opt-out of cookies from our first-party ad serving vendor, Google. The link is https://adssettings.google.com/authenticatedThird-Party and Online Behavioral Advertising Opt-out – Please visit this link to opt-out of cookies from more than 50 major third-party behavioral advertising providers. The link is http://www.aboutads.info/choices/We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any PII from any source unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.Accuracy of InformationYou are responsible for the personally identifiable information that you provide through MarksandHarrison.com. Because our firm strives to maintain the accuracy of information collected through this site, we permit and strongly encourage you to correct any inaccuracies in the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit to this site.Questions?If you have any questions or concerns regarding the online privacy policy for MarksandHarrison.com, or if you wish to use an alternative method to provide us with information, please contact us at:Marks & Harrison1500 Forest AvenueRichmond, VA 23229(804) 282-0999abarr@marksandharrison.com
Get a Free Consultation
Name*
Phone or Email*
What are you interested in?
Personal Injury Auto Accidents Social Security Disability Workers' Compensation Other
Comments*
Send To Our Attorneys
Subscribe To Our Newsletter
The use of the Internet or this form for communication with the firm or any individual member of the firm does not establish an attorney-client relationship. By submitting, you agree to our Privacy Policy.
Need Help? Contact Us Now (800) 283-2202
Contact Us Online
What Our Clients Say
“They sent somebody to visit me in the hospital and get my side of the story (totally free). I was assigned Mr. Crawford and told that we had a case. Fast forward about 9 months later and I received literally 14x what the insurance company had offered me. This is after the lawyer and medical fees as well. So basically this was totally free and I barely had to do anything I am so glad I called Marks and Harrison and I will be recommending them to all of my family and friends.” — Robert Smith
See More Testimonials
Richmond
Richmond 1500 Forest Ave, Rm 100 Richmond, VA 23229
Phone: 804-286-2770
More Info Directions
Chesterfield
Chesterfield 15001 Dogwood Villas Dr. Chesterfield, VA 23832
Phone: 804-662-5882
More Info Directions
Harrisonburg
Harrisonburg 337 East Market Street Harrisonburg, VA 22801
Phone: (540) 433-1738
More Info Directions
Hopewell
Hopewell 2141 E. Hundred Rd Chester, VA 23836
Fredericksburg
Fredericksburg 5440 Jefferson Davis Hwy Fredericksburg, VA 22407
Phone: 540-735-0999
More Info Directions
Staunton
Staunton 206 Greenville Ave Staunton, VA
24401
Phone: 540-887-1200
More Info Directions
Need Help? Contact Us Now (800) 283-2202
Get a Free Consultation
Name*
Phone or Email*
What are you interested in?
Personal Injury Auto Accidents Social Security Disability Workers' Compensation Other
Comments*
Send To An Experienced Attorney
Subscribe To Our Newsletter
The use of the Internet or this form for communication with the firm or any individual member of the firm does not establish an attorney-client relationship. By submitting, you agree to our Privacy Policy.
Helpful Links:HomeAbout UsMeet Our AttorneysPractice AreasQuestions & AnswersFirms News & PressTestimonialsBlogContact Us
©2020 Marks & Harrison. All Rights Reserved
Site Map
Privacy Policy
Disclaimer
Site by Consultwebs.com: Personal Injury Law Firm Website Designers Lawyer Marketing.
Back To Top
Office Hours
×
